Contact

0724602043 (Mobile) gardnerc953@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/celine-gardner (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Responsive Web Design
Web Development
Event Planning

celine Gardner

--Freelance Web Developer

Grahamstown, Eastern Cape, South Africa

Summary

I possess extensive knowledge in the hospitality industry, woodworking, animal care, bird and bat monitoring, and graphic design. My experience in the hospitality sector has honed my strong leadership and teamwork abilities.

In my previous role as a warehouse manager, I developed micromanagement skills that allowed me to successfully oversee larger tasks. My background in the hospitality industry, combined with my experience as an SPCA assistant, has enhanced my interpersonal skills.

I am also a graphic designer and currently training to become a web developer. I studied graphic design as an art subject in school and further developed my skills through freelance work. This year (2024), I began a web development course with FreeCodeCamp, and I am in the process of obtaining my certification.

My very first paying job was in high school as a waitress for weddings. I have managed to step up the ladder within the 3 years at GO-Events

from being a casual waitress and bartender to a full-time eventing staff and Warehouse Manager.

During the period that I have been casually working for GO-Events, I was a carpenter assistant, where I got to build garden benches, plant boxes, stools, and more. For my free days/weekends, I worked at the SPCA in Grahamstown where I cleaned kennels and worked in the office.

In the season, I worked at a beach bar where I was a bartender and sometimes waitressing.

I also did carcass searching for a 5-month contract at the wind turbines. My job was to look for bird and bat carcasses that are affected by the turbines.

Data was collected by marking a waypoint on the GPS where the carcass was found to determine the actual cause of death and the

distance from the turbine itself.

One thing I have learned about myself within the past experiences is that I absolutely love learning new things.

I believe that Web Development would be able to offer what I am looking for.

This is a forever learning field which I believe is perfect for me, especially since I have a designing eye.

I want to create a webpage/app/animations that are visually pleasing, interactive, professional, and fun.

So far, I have been ticking my goals checklist within web development.

My main goal is to be able to get familiar with back-end development and animations.

Experience

Inkululeko Wildlife Services Carcass searching January 2024 - May 2024 (5 months) South Africa

GO-Events

Event Staff

April 2020 - May 2024 (4 years 2 months)

Grahamstown, Eastern Cape, South Africa

Bartender:

Stocking of pre event bar fridge and ensuring garnish and bar equipment is in order

Taking table orders and execution there of (both tab and cash methods)

Pouring of drinks / shooters

Ensuring ice is readily available

Keeping the work area spill free, clean and tidy

Maintaining conversation with clients

Re-Stocking of bar fridges

Evening stock stake of bar stock

Waitress:

Keep working spaces and eating tables clean Serving of 3 course meals

Page 2 of 4

Handling dietary requirements

Assist kitchen staff with plating / garnishing of plates

Setting up and breaking down of events:

Delivery and collection of event infrastructure

Repair and maintenance to various event infrastructure

Event installations – assisting with draping, florals, basic lighting and setting of tables

Basic management of staff and team leader

Communicate and ensure smooth relations with external suppliers such as DJ's and florists etc.

Junior management and supervision of events schedules.

SPCA

SPCA assistant

March 2022 - May 2023 (1 year 3 months)

Grahamstown, Eastern Cape, South Africa

Assisting with walk in clients

Assisting with telephonic clients inquiries and requirements

Clean and disinfecting of cubicles

Feeding and supplying fresh water

Assisting clients with documentation and various requirements

Kept clean, organized and well- stock workspace

Walk dogs and socialized with the kittens / cats

Jerry's on the dune

Bartender

December 2022 - January 2023 (2 months)

Kenton-on-Sea, Eastern Cape, South Africa

Stocking of pre event bar fridge and ensuring garnish and bar equipment is in order

Taking table orders and execution there of (both tab and cash methods)

Pouring of drinks / shooters

Ensuring ice is readily available

Keeping the work area spill free, clean and tidy

Maintaining conversation with clients

Re-Stocking of bar fridges

Evening stock stake of bar stock

ran shooters bar

advertising of shooters

CASTIM

carpenter

February 2022 - December 2022 (11 months)

Repair and maintenance work on various wooden infrastructure furniture

Building of basic planter boxes and garden furniture

Restoration of furniture

Kept weekly inventory of tools and power equipment

Operate power tools and auxiliary instruments

National Arts pop up event event organizer June 2022 - July 2022 (2 months) Grahamstown, Eastern Cape, South Africa

Advertising and promotion of event

Event organizing Assistant

Ticket sales

Entrances and cash sales

Albany museum
painter and maintenance
March 2022 - June 2022 (4 months)
Grahamstown, Eastern Cape, South Africa

Painted walls and ceilings of art galleries
Removing old paint
filling holes / cracks in preparation for new coat
Reached high levels on ladders
Kept a tidy and clean work environment

Education

victoria girls high school

Bachelor's degree · (January 2017 - December 2021)